ellamey.com 2007-12-09

# Ellamey.com - Private Policy

|   
---  
|  |   
---  

| 

---  
**Terms of use**  
Privacy Policy | Abuse Policy  
**Privacy Policy**  
  
Privacy issues are of high priority for us and we follow standard industrial practices to maintain your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**Ellamey does not spam or sell/lease its user information to third parties.**

**Policy Coverage**

This Privacy Policy covers Ellamey's treatment of personally identifiable information that Ellamey collects when you are on the Ellamey site, and when you use Ellamey's services. This policy also covers Ellamey's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Ellamey's business partners share with Ellamey. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Ellamey does not own or control, or to people that Ellamey does not employ or manage.

**Personal Information Collected by Ellamey**

**OPTIONAL PROFILE INFORMATION:** Once you provide the basic information to create an account, you will have the opportunity to provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, interests, professional and academic background and favorites. Provision of this additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional; it allows you to better identify yourself and create superior networking opportunities with other through shared contexts, but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities on Ellamey. Your Profile information can only be viewed by other Ellamey visitors or registered members or only by the members of your personal network, depending on the option you choose.  
  
Top  
  
**INTERNET COMMUNICATION PROTOCOL INFORMATION:** The communication standards of the Internet industry transmit the URL of the site from which you visit Ellamey, the IP address of your computer, the IP address of your ISP, various attributes of your computer such as operating system, resolution and browser software, and the date and time of your various requests for pages on Ellamey. Ellamey file logging system automatically logs all of this information in its log files for its analysis.  
  
Top  
  
**Use of Information by Ellamey**

Ellamey is an online website that offers a variety of services designed to connect people from around the world. The information, whether personal information of any form of self-expression is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Ellamey also collects additional information in order to operate and improve our service. Invictus Technology Solutions [P] Ltd., is the sole owner of the information collected on the Ellamey site.

**VISIBILITY OF NETWORK LINKAGES:** Where applicable, the path of members that connect you with another member of your network will be displayed to that member. This network path will not be shown to those who are not members of your personal network.

**VISIBILITY OF PUBLIC CREATIVE CONTRIBUTIONS:** In addition to being a social and professional networking site, Ellamey also provides a variety of forums for its members to express themselves in the form of articles, columns, opinions, comments, reviews, art and photographs. Since this expression is linked to the member's identity and the expression is in the public domain, the compilation of a member's creative contributions to Ellamey will be visible to all visitors of Ellamey whether or not they are registered members of Ellamey.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES:** Ellamey takes your privacy very seriously. Ellamey will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties unless it is to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. As an example, we send your information to a credit card processing company to process a payment you have made for the use of a Ellamey service. These third parties are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. In addition, Ellamey may share your information to send direct mailers or complimentary coupons/offers to a mailing agency to process postal mailing. Again, such an agency would be bound by strict confidentiality agreements that limit their use of such information.  
  
Top  
  
**EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS:** Ellamey generally communicates with you as a registered member of Ellamey through the primary email that you have specified at the time of registration.  Your email address is never shared with anybody within or outside Ellamey. Ellamey uses this email address to send you three types of communications:

  * Sending you emails related to the proper functioning of your account (e.g. when you receive a response to renew your account.)
  * Sending you occasional announcements about changes in Ellamey's policies or promotions introduction of new services  

**PARTNERING WITH OTHERS:** Ellamey may partner with other online services to offer a combined service. Whenever we offer such combined services, Ellamey will make it clear who the partner is and it will be entirely up to you to use or not to use the service. When any personal information is passed along the partner you will be informed prior to that sharing.

**PROVISION OF AGGREGATE DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES:** Ellamey reserves the right to provide aggregate demographic information of its member base to advertisers and others so as to attract pertinent advertisers to advertise on Ellamey. We do not share personal information of individual users with advertisers.  
  
Top  
  
**DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW:** It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith and belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
  
**Abuse Policy**  
  
Ellamey.com is committed to ensuring and enforcing a safe and friendly online community space for all our members. To this effect, we have come up with a Policy on Abuse that we would like all our members to be aware of. These rules govern the use of the Ellamey.com website and its product/service offerings and we would like all our members to cooperate in complying with these rules so that everyone can have a pleasant experience.

**Conduct and use of language:**

  * Member contributions must be civil and tasteful and must not be malicious or designed to offend. Use of swear-words or profanity is strictly prohibited.
  * Do not refer to the personality of other participants or attack an individual’s character or personally insult another member. Do not use the Network to harass, threaten or verbally abuse or intimidate anyone, or behave in any manner that would cause annoyance or distress to other members.
  * Members of Ellamey.com may not insult or defame the site, including any of its employees, moderators or freelancers. You may not post the contents (in part or whole) of any email that you may receive from any Ellamey.com employee(s) and/or moderator.
  * Do not to post any material that is obscene, defamatory, profane, libelous, threatening, harassing, abusive, hateful or embarrassing towards other person(s) or an entity. We encourage a healthy exchange of opinions and disagreements. By all means, challenge an opinion – but please do it respectfully. Name-calling, insults and use of foul or abusive language will not be tolerated. This includes the use of offensive member Display Names and URLs (your personal website address on Ellamey.com).
  * Please be sure before you divulge the details of your identity or personal information in your post(s), including photos of yourself or your family and friends. Anything posted online is accessible to the entire internet community and Ellamey.com is not liable in cases where such information is misused. Please be aware of the general dangers of online information sharing like identity theft, phishing and other fraudulent activites.
  * Members of Ellamey.com are not permitted to collect or distribute personal data concerning other members at any time.
  * A member of Ellamey.com must not impersonate another member.

Top  
  
**Advertising and Spamming:**   

  * No advertising or promotion is allowed except where it is for an event, publication or similar item that has direct relevance to the subject of discussion and is non-commercial in nature. Please bear in mind that the space on the Network is for creative contributions by members and not for personal advertising or promotion(s). Information about locating and sharing knowledge and expertise is welcomed, but must have relevance to the topic on which an opinion is expressed or a discussion is initiated.
  * Do not post chain letters, promote pyramid schemes or recruit members for any “network marketing” or “multilevel marketing” businesses.
  * Do not recruit members to join another website forum or chat group, whether personal or otherwise. If you have a suggestion for a new forum, please contact us or send your queries to member relations.
  * Ellamey.com encourages healthy discussion on the topics that members contribute to in forums and where relevant, members are allowed to post links to their content. However, overt promotion of, or inappropriate links to other known commercial websites on any forum are not permitted and will be removed. If you are unsure whether a link or a posting is allowed, please send your queries to member relations. The definition of an “appropriate link” is one that is relevant to both the posting and the forum topic. A “commercial” site is considered as one which promotes a product or service for a price or for other consideration that suggests it is a for-profit business.

Top  
  
**Copyrighted Material:** Uploading copies of copyrighted material as a whole or in part on Ellamey.com without explicit permission from the copyright owner shall be deemed to infringe on the copyright and this applies to materials such as text, images, music, movies, games, and other software in digital and analog format. Ellamey.com reserves the right to immediately delete such material without prior permission/consultation from the member. If you suspect that an image submitted to Ellamey.com is copyright protected and has been used fraudulently, please contact us immediately or send us an email to: [ info@ellamey.com](mailto:info@ellamey.com)   
**Safety Guidelines:** Ellamey.com is always reaching out to a wider audience by showcasing the best of our member contributions. However, in doing so, we will not allow to upload anything on the site that we think could be potentially endangering or is inflammatory or embarrassing to our members. It also helps members to be aware of certain things in the interest of their safety.

  * All members are responsible for the safety of their personal information. We recommend that members do not disclose their names, addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers or other personal information online.
  * All members need to be aware that when they upload their photos to the site, the photos are not only visible to the entire internet community but can also be downloaded, since any image that can be displayed on a computer screen can be saved by the person viewing it. It is technically not possible to prevent this and hence Ellamey.com cannot be held liable in such cases. If you are worried about someone else viewing or saving your images then please do not submit them.
  * Ellamey.com encourages healthy discussion on the topics that members contribute in forums and are relevant and also members are allowed to post links to their content. However, overt promotion or inappropriate links to other known commercial websites on any forum are not permitted and will be removed. If you are unsure whether a link or a posting is allowed, please send your queries to [ info@ellamey.com](mailto:info@ellamey.com) . The definition of an “appropriate link” is one that is relevant to both the posting and the forum topic. A “commercial” site is considered as one which promotes a product or service for a price or for other consideration that suggests it is a for-profit business.  

Top  
  
**Legalities:**

  * All members are reminded that they may be held legally accountable for what they say or do online. In particular, members may be held liable for any defamatory comments, threats and/or untrue statements or other illegal and fraudulent claims made by them.
  * Ellamey.com does not endorse the opinions expressed by its members.
  * If any member fails to observe the above rules of conduct at any time, Ellamey.com reserves the right to terminate the membership of the member and/or delete all their contributions (either temporarily or permanently) from the site, depending on the nature and severity of the breach and without prior warning or consent of the member. 

Registration as a Ellamey.com member at any time – past or present and use of the Ellamey.com website and all its product/service offerings will be taken as acceptance of the above rules of conduct. Ellamey.com’s decision on all matters is final and binding on its members. Legal jurisdiction for all disputes is the High Court of Chennai, India.

Ellamey.com endeavours to foster a vibrant online community of Indians worldwide by providing a platform with global reach to express themselves and connect with other people, thus forming mutually beneficial relationships. We are here to serve our members 24x7 and use all feedback to refine and improve the online experience for our members. You can reach TEAM Ellamey anytime by writing to [info@ellamey.com](mailto:info@ellamey.com)  and we will respond to you in a timely manner. We hope you have an enjoyable and rewarding experience on the Ellamey.com. Welcome aboard!  

| ADVERTISEMENT  
---
